Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
Red Hot Organization Archive
1989-2004
Fales Library and Special Collections
Red Hot Organization
Carlin, John, 1955-
MSS.191
40.25 Linear Feet
The Red Hot Organization is an international organization dedicated to fighting AIDS through pop culture. First founded as King Cole, Inc. by Leigh Blake and John Carlin in 1989, Red Hot Organization has since produced fourteen albums, related television programs and media events incorporating the talents of performers, visual artists, producers and directors to raise funds and awareness for HIV and AIDS. The collection contains the production files of the organization's projects, including administrative records and financial files, and merchandise such as CDs, videos, and t-shirts. The collection also contains raw and finished film, video, and audio media, which is currently unprocessed and not available for research use.
Historical Note
The Red Hot Organization is an international organization dedicated to fighting AIDS through pop culture. First founded as King Cole, Inc. by Leigh Blake and John Carlin in 1989, Red Hot Organization has since produced fourteen albums, related television programs and media events incorporating the talents of performers, visual artists, producers and directors to raise funds and awareness for HIV and AIDS.
To date, Red Hot's efforts have donated nearly 7 million dollars for AIDS relief around the world. Besides funding AIDS research and education, Red Hot awarded grants in cooperation with existing AIDS organizations, such as the National Minority AIDS Council. Revenues from the sale of albums and videos in foreign countries remained within each respective country to help support local AIDS prevention and relief.
(Reference: www.redhot.org)
Scope and Content
The Red Hot Organization Archive contains the production files of the organization's projects, including administrative records and financial files, and merchandise such as CDs, videos, and t-shirts. The collection also contains raw and finished film, video, and audio media, which is currently unprocessed and not available for research use. CDs and other media found in Merchandise series may be accessible upon request.
Numerous oversize items found at the end of each of the series include t-shirts, posters, and other oversize promotional material housed in boxes.
Arrangement
Red Hot Organization Collection is generally organized into series by Red Hot Organization projects undertaken between 1990 and 2005. The series are arranged chronologically according to each project's release date.
Materials within series are arranged alphabetically, with all efforts made to preserve the original titles and classifications of the collection.
Red Hot Organization Collection is generally organized into series by Red Hot Organization projects undertaken between 1990 and 2005. The series are arranged chronologically according to each project's release date.
Materials within series are arranged alphabetically, with all efforts made to preserve the original titles and classifications of the collection.
The collection is organized into 24 series:
Missing Title
Series I. Red Hot + Blue
Series II. Red Hot + Dance
Series III. No Alternative
Series IV. Red Hot + Publish
Series V. Red Hot + Country
Series VI. Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool
Series VII. Red Hot + Bothered
Series VIII. The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
Series IX. America is Dying Slowly
Series X. Red Hot + Rio
Series XI. Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
Series XII. Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute")
Series XIII. Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon
Series XIV. Red Hot and Rhapsody
Series XV. Optic Nerve: David Wojnarowicz on CD-Rom
Series XVI. Red Hot + Indigo
Series XVII. Artists Against AIDS Worldwide - "What's Goin' On"
Series XVIII. Red Hot + Riot
Series XIX. General Red Hot Organization
Series XX - Series XXIII contain production elements and are closed to researchers.
Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage
Oversize - Series I: Red Hot + Blue
Oversize - Series II: Red Hot + Dance
Oversize - Series III: No Alternative
Oversize - Series V: Red Hot + Country
Oversize - Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool
Oversize - Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered
Oversize - Series VIII: The Beat Experience/Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
Oversize - Series IX: America os Dying Slowly
Oversize - Series X: Red Hot + Rio
Oversize - Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
Oversize - Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute")
Oversize - Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon
Oversize - Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
Oversize - Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo
Oversize - Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
Oversize - Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
Provenance
The Red Hot Organization Archive was donated to the Fales Library by Red Hot's founder, John Carlin, in 2006.
Access Restrictions
Repository permission is required for access. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Beat generation.; Safe sex in AIDS prevention.; Haring, Keith; Lindsay, Arto; Byrd, Donald, 1949-; Byrne, David, 1952-; Smith, Patti; Baraka, Amiri, 1934-2014; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Araki, Gregg; Waits, Tom, 1949-; Harry, Debbie; O'Hara, Frank, 1926-1966; Livingston, Jennie; Whitney Museum of American Art; Davis, Tamra; Ono, Yōko; Wojnarowicz, David; ACT UP (Organization); Carlin, John, 1955-
- Series I: Red Hot + Blue, 105071
  Scope and Contents
  Red Hot + Blue was released in 1990 and was the first in the Red Hot series. Red Hot + Blue featured contemporary pop performers reinterpreting the songs of Cole Porter. An accompanying television special featured videos for all but two songs.
  In 2006 Red Hot + Blue was re-issued on a special two-disc set including the original CD remastered, and a DVD of the home video.
  (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 105072
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1991-1992; cuid7167; 151133 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7168; 151750 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Authorization for broadcast of Erasure's "Too Darn Hot" on Alive TV, 1992; cuid7169; 105156 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Authorization for inclusion of Annie Lennox's "Ev'rytime We Say Goodbye" in "Prelude to a Kiss" OST, 1992; cuid7170; 105134 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Binder, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 1-4)
    - Bravo Company, 1991; cuid7171; 105154 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Budgets, 1990; cuid7172; 105163 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Canadian Foundation for AIDS Research, 1991; cuid7173; 151287 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Canal+ Productions, 1990-1991; cuid7174; 145291 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Charity international, 1990-1991; cuid7175; 105157 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Chrysalis Records, 1990; cuid7176; 105139 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Chrysalis Records - England - Re-releases and sales reports, 1990; cuid7177; 105155 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Contact sheets ("Red Hot and Blue Bible"), cuid7178; 139301 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Contracts for re-releases, 1990-1993; cuid7179; 105137 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Blake, Leigh to Carlin, John, 1990; cuid7180; 155306 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Costs, 1991; cuid7181; 155307 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Distributions, 1996; cuid7182; 153947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - EMI Italiana Spa re: Italian charities, 1991; cuid7183; 151140 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Foreign TV rights, 1990; cuid7184; 105138 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Information packet, [n.d.]; cuid7185; 105166 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Invoices, 1990-1991; cuid7186; 151139 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Island Records Ltd, 1991; cuid7187; 145308 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Kostich, Craig, 1991; cuid7188; 151301 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - List of media, [n.d.]; cuid7189; 139300 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Meeting notes, 1989; cuid7190; 139299 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Merchandise - invoices and sales summaries, 1990; cuid7191; 105165 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Merchandising - Financials, 1991; cuid7192; 154029 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Merchandising - T-shirts/Artwork, 1990; cuid7193; 105164 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Merchandising - T-shirts/Artwork, 1990; cuid7194; 105152 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - MTV, 1990; cuid7195; 145293 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - The New York Festivals, 1992; cuid7196; 151134 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Palace Group Ltd re: production of television special, 1990; cuid7197; 105136 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Pioneer LDCA, Inc., 1991; cuid7198; 145292 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Record co-releases, 2002; cuid7199; 105135 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Red Hot and Blue Merchandising Limited Report and Accounts for the Period Ending 30 November 1991, cuid7200; 155304 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Red, Hot & Blue Ballet Project, 1991; cuid7201; 151293 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Royalties, 1991-1994; cuid7202; 161765 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Royalties/Finances, 1990-1992; cuid7203; 105158 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Safe Sex Campaign, 1991-1994; cuid7204; 139227 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Signed record releases, 1990; cuid7205; 105133 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7206; 151667 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 105073
    - Bag - "Entertainment Weekly Honors Red Hot & Blue", [n.d.]; cuid7207; 131852 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Cards promoting Red, Hot + Blue video release party hosted by The Institute of Contemporary Art, 1991; cuid7208; 131859 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Condoms - Red Hot + Blue, cuid7209; 131850 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Flier ads - merchandise, cuid7210; 151830 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Invitations to "A Swell Party", 1990; cuid7211; 156576 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Invitations to "The release of 6 West Home Video's Red Hot & Blue", 1991; cuid7212; 131858 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Invitation to press conference for Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7213; 131860 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous, [n.d.]; cuid7214; 131867 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Press clippings - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7215; 138324 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Press clippings - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7216; 154086 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Press clippings - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7217; 161764 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Press clippings - Red Hot + Blue, 1990-1992; cuid7218; 105162 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Press clippings from BMG Video International, c.a. 1992; cuid7219; 151137 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings - Safe Sex Campaign, 1991; cuid7220; 139226 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Press packet (French), [n.d.]; cuid7221; 154150 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Press release draft, 1991; cuid7222; 151138 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Programme for The Cambridge University Fashion Show for Red Hot and Blue, 1991; cuid7223; 131866 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Promotional single: "I've Got You Under My Skin," Neneh Cherry, 1990; cuid7224; 131853 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Format
      VHS
    - Stationery - Red Hot + Blue, [n.d.]; cuid7225; 131861 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 105075
    - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7226; 128620 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Audio cassette
    - Red Hot + Blue, 1990; cuid7227; 131848 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      General
      Labeled "Reference copy"
      Audio compact disc
    - Red Hot + Blue, alternate packaging designed and produced by Parkway Studios in conjunction with Cutterdies, 1990; cuid7228; 131854 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Red Hot + Blue, EMI (Malaysia) distribution edition, [n.d.]; cuid7229; 131846 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Red Hot + Blue, Portugal distribution edition, 1990; cuid7230; 161779 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Double audio cassette
    - Red Hot + Blue cassette liner notes, 1990; cuid7231; 131849 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Red Hot + Blue CD liner notes, 1990; cuid7232; 131845 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Red Hot + Blue CD liner notes, 1990; cuid7233; 131855 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Red Hot + Blue home video sleeve, 1990; cuid7234; 131862 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Red Hot + Blue microcassette liner notes, 1990; cuid7235; 131865 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Red Hot + Blue special 2-disc edition, 2006; cuid7236; 131844 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Digital Versatile Disc and compact disc
    - Single: "I've Got You Under My Skin," Neneh Cherry, 1990; cuid7237; 131857 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 7 in.
  - Subseries E: Awards, 105076
    - Record of the Year Award, Stereo Review, 1991; cuid7238; 161162 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Subseries H: Audio - Access Copies, cuid7239; 105079
- Series II: Red Hot + Dance, 1992; 105083
  Red Hot + Dance was released in 1992 by Columbia Records, featuring three exclusive tracks from George Michael. Other major dance artists donated tracks, remixed by D.J.s and producers from around the world. An accompanying home video was released by Sony Music Video Enterprises. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  An anomaly exists in Series II: Red Hot + Dance. An additional series, designated as Subseries L, pertains to the legal dispute between George Michael and Sony Music.
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 105085
    - Accounting - "Trust" & "Live", 1991; cuid7240; 154031 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Accounts/Budget, 1991-1992; cuid7241; 105194 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Agreements, 1991; cuid7242; 151148 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - AIDS Trust of Australia, 1992; cuid7243; 151129 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Art against AIDS, 1992; cuid7244; 151100 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7245; 151741 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Banking, 1992-1993; cuid7246; 105207 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Budget/Expenses, 1991-1992; cuid7247; 105197 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Budget/Expenses, 1991-1992; cuid7248; 144566 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Budget/Expenses for album launch party, 1992; cuid7249; 147634 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - C + C Music Factory, 1992; cuid7250; 147637 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Call sheets, 1991; cuid7251; 147677 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Cassette/CD/Album, 1993-1994; cuid7252; 105189 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - City to City events, 1991; cuid7253; 147668 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Club King Co., 1991-1992; cuid7254; 151276 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Contracts, 1991; cuid7255; 147670 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence -- miscellaneous, 1991; cuid7256; 147676 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Creditors lists, 1992; cuid7257; 151351 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Crew lists, [n.d.]; cuid7258; 147673 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Disco, [n.d.]; cuid7259; 154172 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Contains sticky note listing artists and song titles, and a letter from The Burt Bacharach Music Group.
    - Dreamtime Productions s.r.l., 1991; cuid7260; 151130 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Event passes: V.I.P. and All Access, cuid7261; 151821 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Foreign monies, 1996; cuid7262; 105196 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Granada Television Limited, 1991; cuid7263; 151149 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Grants, 1996; cuid7264; 154127 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Heller, Liz (Island Visual Arts/Polygram Video US), 1991-1992; cuid7265; 145313 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Home video, [n.d.]; cuid7266; 105167 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Invoices: A--H, 1991-1992; cuid7267; 151356 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Invoices: I--Z, 1991-1992; cuid7268; 151357 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1990-1992; cuid7269; 151360 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1991; cuid7270; 151361 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1992; cuid7271; 151362 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1991-1992; cuid7272; 151363 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1991; cuid7273; 151367 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - INXS, 1991; cuid7274; 151136 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - John Howard Hotel re: Todd Terry bill, 1992; cuid7275; 147633 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Keith Haring Estate, 1992; cuid7276; 105206 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - MTV, 1991 - 1992; cuid7278; 139298 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Notes, [n.d.]; cuid7279; 151300 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Orders/invoices, 1991-1992; cuid7280; 147678 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Palace Group of Companies Ltd, 1991; cuid7281; 151275 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pellingham, Mark: TV special/home video treatment, [n.d.]; cuid7282; 147669 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Picture negative reports, 1991; cuid7283; 147671 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Releases and re-releases, 1992; cuid7284; 105190 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Royalties, 1995-1998; cuid7285; 153888 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Schedules, 1991; cuid7286; 147672 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Sire Records, 1991; cuid7287; 145314 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 6-month cashflow, 1992; cuid7288; 147569 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Sony Music, 1990-1992; cuid7289; 105191 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Sony Music: Correspondence, 1996-1999; cuid7290; 153952 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Sony Music royalties dispute: 1992/3 correspondence; locally retained royalties, 1992-1993; cuid7291; 151685 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Sony Music royalties dispute: 1994 correspondence, cuid7292; 151684 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Sony Music royalties dispute: Settlement; 1995 correspondence, 1995-1997; cuid7293; 151670 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7294; 151668 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 105086
    - Badges - Red Hot + Dance, [n.d.]; cuid7295; 151824 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Dance, [n.d.]; cuid7296; 151831 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Invitations to "A Red Hot Party honoring those who have given life to Red Hot + Dance", 1992; cuid7297; 151822 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Paper bag - Red Hot + Dance, 1992; cuid7298; 151817 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Postcards - "safe sex is hot sex," couples, 1992; cuid7299; 161289 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Postcards - "safe sex is hot sex," female couple, 1992; cuid7300; 161288 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Postcards - "safe sex is hot sex," male couple, 1992; cuid7301; 161287 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Press clippings, 1991-1992; cuid7302; 161780 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Press clippings, 1992; cuid7303; 139281 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Press release draft, 1992; cuid7304; 139289 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Promotional single: "Too Funky," George Michael, 1992; cuid7305; 151820 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Stationery - Red Hot + Dance, [n.d.]; cuid7306; 151299 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Stickers - Red Hot + Dance, [n.d.]; cuid7307; 151818 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 105087
    - Animation still: "Everybody's World AIDS Day" by ARTONIC, c.a. 1991; cuid7308; 147674 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Photograph: Captioned "sent adrift on memory bliss of you -- three bro's from N.J. the Garden State love Ed", [n.d.]; cuid7309; 147667 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Dance event (BINDER), cuid7310; 151744 (Box 37)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 105088
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace", 1992; cuid7311; 151823 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace", 1992; cuid7312; 151819 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Compact disc
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace", 1992; cuid7313; 151828 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Sound disc: Analog; 7 in.
    - Red Hot + Dance, 1992; cuid7314; 151825 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Red Hot + Dance, 1992; cuid7315; 151826 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Red Hot + Dance CD liner notes, 1992; cuid7316; 151829 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries L: George Michael v. Sony legal dispute, 139278
    - Correspondence: Martin Green Ravden, 1993; cuid7317; 139279 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Press clippings, 1992; cuid7318; 139280 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series III: No Alternative, 1993; 105084
  Scope and Content
  No Alternative was released in 1993 by Arista Records. An MTV special and home video featuring live performances, music videos, and information about AIDS was released by PolyGram Video in 1993. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 105097
    - "Trout" - Neneh Cherry re: "Athens, Georgia 1993", 1994; cuid7319; 152116 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Agreements (including draft), 1993-1994; cuid7320; 147715 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - All of No Alt, 1996; cuid7321; 160523 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      SyQuest 88 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
      Separated Materials
      The removable hard drive has been moved to Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage.
    - American Music Club / Warner Bros. Records Inc., 1993; cuid7322; 152080 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Araki, Gregg, 1993; cuid7323; 153839 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Arista Records contacts, [n.d.]; cuid7324; 150962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Arista Records correspondence, 1993; cuid7325; 151086 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7326; 151742 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Audit, 1996; cuid7327; 161810 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Audit - Arista Records, 1997-1999; cuid7328; 161811 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Bad Moon, 1993; cuid7329; 151087 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Beastie Boys, 1993; cuid7330; 152112 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Breeders, 1993-1994; cuid7331; 152113 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Brockum Group (Merchandising), 1994; cuid7332; 128580 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Budget & billing status, 1992-1993; cuid7333; 152158 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Budget/Expenses, 1993; cuid7334; 151088 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Buffalo Tom / Beggars Banquet Records, 1993-1994; cuid7335; 152115 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - BUREAU, 1994; cuid7336; 152155 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Channel Four Television, 1993; cuid7337; 151091 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Clearances, 1993-1994; cuid7338; 152079 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Contact information, [n.d.]; cuid7339; 153832 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Davis, Tamra, 1993-1995; cuid7340; 152117 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Gold Mountain Entertainment, 1993-1994; cuid7341; 151095 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Goo Goo Dolls, 1993; cuid7342; 152120 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - In a New Light '94 - Permission to use, 1994; cuid7343; 152118 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Intra-organization correspondence, 1993; cuid7344; 151085 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - IRS Records, 1993; cuid7345; 151093 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Liner notes draft, 1993; cuid7346; 150959 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Livingston, Jenny, 1993; cuid7347; 152119 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - McKay, Jim / Stipe, Michael (R.E.M) short film: "Athens, Georgia 1993", cuid7348; 152122 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - McLachlan, Sarah's "Hold On" re: inclusion in 4-song cassette sampler (Restricted), 1993-1994; cuid7349; 152126 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Manning, Barbara (Restricted), 1993; cuid7350; 152121 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Mould, Bob, 1993-1994; cuid7351; 153842 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - MTV, 1993; cuid7352; 151098 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - MTV / TV show, 1993; cuid7353; 153831 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Nirvana, 1993 - 1994; cuid7354; 153840 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Notes and drafts, 1993; cuid7355; 151096 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Pavement, 1993; cuid7356; 152127 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Pirner, Dave (Soul Asylum), 1993; cuid7357; 151097 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - PolyGram, 1993; cuid7358; 151094 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Programme outlines, 1993; cuid7359; 151089 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Richman, Jonathan, 1993; cuid7360; 152123 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Royalties, 2000; cuid7361; 154256 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Royalties audit, 1993-1999; cuid7362; 152078 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Royalty statement - Australia, 1995-1996; cuid7363; 153898 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Sales breakdown: International, 1994-1997; cuid7364; 153971 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Smashing Pumpkins, 1993-1994; cuid7365; 152128 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Patti, 1993-1994; cuid7366; 152129 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Sonic Youth, 1993-1994; cuid7367; 152130 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Soul Asylum, 1993-1994; cuid7368; 153841 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Soundgarden, 1993-1994; cuid7369; 153838 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Straitjacket Fits, 1993; cuid7370; 153837 (Box 4, Folder 62)